Agency for International Development Contract with the Federal University of Cearaá, Brazil papers. 1962-1973
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Agency for International Development Contract with the Federal University of Ceará, Brazil papers, 1962-1973
AZ 441
Correspondence, reports, workbook and historical materials.
Agency for International Development Contract; University of Arizona. College of Agriculture
3.0 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Historical Note
The objectives of the grant project were to ascertain the needs of the agricultural colleges at Fortaleza, Ceará, and Recife, Pernambuco with regard to administration, faculties, facilities, finances, and research programs.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, reports, workbook and historical materials.
Access Terms
United States. Agency for International Development
Rural development -- Brazil
Agricultural development projects -- Brazil
Brazil Project
1950-1974
Correspondence
Container List
- Historical Material, 1918-1979 (Folder 1)
  Castro, Francisco Alves de Andrade e: ENSINO E DESENVOLVIMENTO DAS CIENCIAS AGRARIAS NO NORDESTE (CEARA); 1918-1978. Fortaleza, BNB, 1979.
- General Correspondence; 3 vols., 1962-1966 (Folder 2)
- General Correspondence; 3 vols., 1967-1970 (Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1963-1973 (Folder 4)
  General Correspondence, 1971-1973
  Correspondence: William J. Pistor, Chief of Party, 1963-1966
  Correspondence: William J. Pistor, Chief of Party, and E.B. Stanley, Campus Coordinator, 1964-1966
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Folder 5)
- Workbook, 1962-1966 (Folder 5)
- Semi-Annual Reports, 1964-1973 (Folder 6)
  Lacks: 12th, 18th
- Final Report: Ten Years in Brazil, 1975 (Folder 6)
- Chief of Party: Monthly Reports, 1966-1973 (Folder 7)
- Monthly Reports to the Chief of Party, 1970-1973 (Folder 7)
- Short Term Staff Reports, 1962-1973 (Folder 7)
- End of Tour Reports (Faculty members on contract), 1964-1973 (Folder 8)